Guide to the James G. Harbord Papers 1902-1949 MS 1493
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: General correspondence
  - Subseries I.1: Correspondence A-Z
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Unemployment Relief", September-November 1931 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Union League Campaign Committee", 1928 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-United States Junior Naval Rescue", 1921-1926 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-United States Seniors Golf Association", 1926-1947 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Verdun International World War Memorial", 1923-1933 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Western Railroads", 1933 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", July-September 1947 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", May-June 1947 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", January-March 1947 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", August-December 1946 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", October 1945-August 1946 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", January-September 1945 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", April-December 1944 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", January-March 1944 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", September-December 1943 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", June-August 1943 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", December 1942-May 1943 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", October-December 1942 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", June-September 1942 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", October 1941-May 1942 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", June-September 1941 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", March-May 1941 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", December 1940-January 1941 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", July-November 1940 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", January-June 1940 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", December 1939 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", December 1939 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", March-November 1937 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", December 1936-February 1937 (Offsite-box 32, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", July-December 1936 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", December 1937-May 1938 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Miscellaneous", September 1938-February 1939 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", June 1935 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 4)
      The "Memberships-Etc." category of the correspondence was mis-filed and is spread across boxes 29, 30, and 33.
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", May 1935 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", Mid-Late April 1935 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", Early-Mid April 1935 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", March 1935 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", February 1935 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", January 1935 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", 1934 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", 1934 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", 1931-1933 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", 1925-1930 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", 1923-1924 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence "MI-MY", 1945-1947 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 15)
      This note pertains to all "MI-MY" folders:
      Includes memos from the Monterey Peninsula Country Club, which Harbord suggested be geared to service men. This marketing plan turned out to be a great success (1945); a tract on the "American National Policy Regarding International Trade Agreements and Cartels" (1945); correspondence regarding the President's Industrial Recovery Act, 1933; report from "South American Oil Reports" by Michael O'Shaughnessy called the "Stabilization of Industry"; correspondence regarding the Philippines and General Wood.
    - Correspondence "MI-MY", 1943-1944 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence "MI-MY", 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence "MI-MY", 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 33, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence "MI-MY", 1935-1936 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "MI-MY", 1937-1938 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "MI-MY", 1933-1934 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "MI-MY", 1931-1932 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "MI-MY", 1928-1930 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence "MI-MY", 1926-1927 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "MI-MY", 1925 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "MI-MY", 1923-1924 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "Miscellaneous", 1942-1947 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 9)
      "Miscellaneous folders consist primarily of inter-office notes, phone and visit messages, and received poems, clippings, mailers.
    - Correspondence "Miscellaneous", 1938-1941 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "Miscellaneous", 1935-1937 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "Miscellaneous", 1932-1934 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence "Miscellaneous", 1931 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence "Miscellaneous", 1927-1930 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence "Miscellaneous", 1926 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence "Miscellaneous", 1917-1925 (Offsite-box 34, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence "Moran v. Harbord" (Offsite-box 34, Folder 17)
      Lawsuit against the Harbords lodged by a former employee (cook) who fell down their stairs.
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1947 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 1)
      Notable correspondents include Edward J. Nally (VP and general manager of American Marconi Company; first president of RCA); National Geographic Society; Rauf Orbay (Ottoman naval officer, Turkish statesman and diplomat).
      Subjects discussed include Harbord's role as chairman of RCA; real estate market in Washington; health issues; National Council of the Citizens Committee for a National War Service Act; books; vacation to Rancho Santa Fe; domestic life in Rye; bonds; and Domestic help (the "servant problem").
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1946 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 2)
      Letters discuss health; deaths; books; Philippine Society dinner; Domestic help (Complaints about servants/lack of servants); and Harbord's vacation in Death Valley.
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1945 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 3)
      Notable correspondents include Basil O'Connor (American lawyer. In cooperation with US President Franklin D. Roosevelt he started two foundations for the rehabilitation of polio patients and the research on polio prevention and treatment. From 1944 to 1949 he was chairman and president of the American Red Cross and from 1945 to 1950 he was chairman of the League of Red Cross Societies). Letters discuss Harbord's poor health, plans to visit Death Valley, Hiroshima, and Servants.
    - Correspondence "N-O", July-December 1944 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 4)
      Letters discuss health problems, Japanese occupation, the death of President Quezon [president of the Commonwealth of the Philippines], and the difficulty finding enough servants and a cook.
    - Correspondence "N-O", January-June 1944 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 5)
      Letters discuss Mrs. Harbord's neuritis, servants, diet and fitness plan, the War Report, General of the Armies Bill, and women marines. A letter to "Dear Aunt Kate" [Mrs. T.W.Orendorff] dated March 22, 1944: "I hope your young neighbor boy who calls you 'Dear Aunt Kate' from somewhere out in the Pacific will make good on that killing of a Jap and a German and send you their scalps".
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1943 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1942 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 7)
      Notable correspondents include James Walker Tufts (entrepreneur); Major General John F. O'Ryan (a New York City attorney, politician, government official and military officer. He served as commander of the 27th Division during World War I. He later served as a member of the New York State Transit Commission and as New York City Police Commissioner. During World War II he was New York State Civil Defense Director). Letters discuss girl home makers, the Emma Harbord Memorial, the Army Relief Society, the Seabord Railway, servants, Wrigley's chewing gum being "hit by the war," WAAC and WAVE, Roosevelt, Churchill, and the Second Airborne Division. There are also pamphlets for hotels in North Carolina and Florida.
      Letter to Mary Louise 12/8/1942: "The two servants are Japanese, as you know, and while we have great confidence in them there are, beyond question, a few people in our neighborhood at Rye who seem to resent our keeping them. They comply with the law and are, as far as their behavior is concerned, better Americans than some of the people who criticize their presence--paying income taxes, having a bank account, and all those things which good citizens are supposed to do."
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1941 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 8)
      Letters discuss Mrs. Harbord's trust, RCA settlement, Hitler, WWII, and health. Interesting letterheads include The Alvarado Hotel (Albuquerque, NM) and the Japanese Embassy. There are pamphlets on "The Public's Platform for Labor Reform" and "The American Forum of the Air."
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1940 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 9)
      Topics include Roosevelt and WWII. There is a calendar from Oberlin College.
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1939 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 10)
      Letters discuss modern art, WWII, Rye, health issues, and Japanese Beetles. There is a pamphlet titled "The Spirit of the Founders of the University of Notre Dame."
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1938 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 11)
      Notable correspondents include R. Nagai, Minister of Communications (Tokyo, Japan). Interesting letterheads include The Philippine Club, New York World's Fair 1939 Incorporated and The Square Table Club. Letters discuss Harbord's Second Marriage to Mrs. Anne Lee Brown, China, Japan, the Disabled Veterans Convention, and Harbord's travel plans (to Tokyo).
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1937 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 12)
      Interesting letterheads include the Brighton Hotel, St. Bartholomew's Church, and the RCA Building. Letters discuss The Emma Harbord Fund, Emma's estate, investments, and Mrs. Harbord's death.
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1936 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 13)
      Letters discuss Emma Harbord's hospital treatment, detective stories, the Hoover Administration and the Philippine Defense Bill.
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1935 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1934 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1933 (Offsite-box 35, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1932 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1931 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "N-O (Appointment of Ovenshine)", 1927-1931 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1930 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1929 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1928 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1927 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1926 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1925 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1924 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1923 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "N-O", 1921-1922 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence "O-(Organizations) RCA", 1922-1942 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence "PA-PL", 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence "PA-PL", 1944-1945 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence "PA-PL", 1943 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence "PA-PL", 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 36, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence "PA-PL", 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "PA-PL", 1936-1938 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "PA-PL", 1934-1935 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "PA-PL", 1932-1934 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "PA-PL", 1931 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence "PA-PL", 1929-1930 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "PA-PL", 1927-1928 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "PA-PL", 1925-1926 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "PA-PL", 1923-1924 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence "Passports", 1923-1924 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 10)
      Includes Mr. and Mrs. Harbord's passports and identification information.
    - Correspondence "PA-PL (Patton- War as I Knew It)" (Offsite-box 37, Folder 11)
      Complete manuscript.
    - Correspondence "PA-PL (Patton Fund for Jensen Memorial)" (Offsite-box 37, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence "Philippine Independence" (Offsite-box 37, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence "Photographs", 1922-1927 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 14)
      This note pertains to all "photographs" folders. Contents include solicitation for copies of photos; photo session; photo retouch; photo autographs; falsified photo scandal including Hoover FBI letter. Many duplicate headshots of Harbord in uniform and at RCA events.
    - Correspondence "Photographs", 1928-1934 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence "Photographs", 1935-1947 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "Photographs-Harbord" (Offsite-box 38, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "Photographs-Harbord Portraits" (Offsite-box 38, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "Photographs-Harbord Military" (Offsite-box 38, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "Photographs-Harbord RCA Studios" (Offsite-box 38, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence "Photographs-Groups and Events" (Offsite-box 38, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "Photographs-Mounted Studio Photos (Harbord and others)" (Offsite-box 38, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "Photographs-People other than Harbord and Pictorial Ephemera" (Offsite-box 38, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "PO-PY", 1941-1947 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 9)
      This note pertains to all "PO-PY" folders. Regular correspondents: Colonel Arthur Poillon; Captain S. T. Polk; Captain Popenos; Colonel Puyol; Mrs. Porter. Common contents consist of speeches (addresses), publications, letters received, biographical sketch of Harbord, book contract, pamphlets.
    - Correspondence "PO-PY", 1937-1940 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "PO-PY", 1931-1936 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "PO-PY", 1927-1930 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 12)
      Correspondence from Colonel Poole. Harbord's address at University of Virginia (Institute of Public Affairs).
    - Correspondence "PO-PY", 1921-1926 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence "Publicity (Misc.)" (Offsite-box 38, Folder 14)
      The "Publicity" folders contain requests for Harbord to attend and participate in various speaking engagements including lectures, luncheons, banquets, symposia, and society dinners. They also contain hardcopies of select speeches and addresses that Harbord gave.
    - Correspondence "Publicity", 1947-1949 (Offsite-box 38, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", 1946 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", 1945 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", 1944 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", January-December1943 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", July-September 1942 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", January-June 1942 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", September-December 1941 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", January-August 1941 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", July-December 1940 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", January-June 1940 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", July-December 1939 (Offsite-box 39, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", May-June 1939 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 1)
      Address containing first-hand accounts of Harbord's experiences in the war, delivered to The Army War College, Washington, D.C. On April 6, 1939. "A Chief of Staff in the Theater of Operations"
    - Correspondence "Publicity", January-April 1939 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 2)
      Newspaper clipping from the Temple Daily Telegram, Temple, Texas, in which Harbord writes on how he believes television has no future.
    - Correspondence "Publicity", November-December 1938 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 3)
      Radio broadcast transcripts, "Observations Around the Pacific III, China, Japan and Manchoukuo, September 13, 1938," "Observations Around the Pacific II, The Philippines," on September 6, 1938.
      Broadcast on the Red Cross, over Radio WEAF, 6:00 p.m., November 17, 1938: "The Red Cross is Here," firsthand accounts of the hurricane that hit New York City in 1930
    - Correspondence "Publicity", April-October 1938 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 4)
      Harbord's thoughts on Japan: address before the America-Japan Society, June 9, 1938, Imperial Hotel
    - Correspondence "Publicity", January-March 1938 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 5)
      Memorial address broadcast over station WJZ and the NBC Blue Network by on behalf of Newton Baker, Secretary of War during WWI, Sunday evening, January 2, 1938, Imperial Hotel
    - Correspondence "Publicity", April-June 1937 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 6)
      Address, "History in the Making and the Writing," January 28, 1938, before the members of the Catholic Writers Guild of America, at De La Salle Institute
      Address, February 15, 1937, to the Henrietta Wells Livermore School of Politics at the Women's National Republican Club
    - Correspondence "Publicity", July-December 1937 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 7)
      Address broadcast over WJZ by General James G. Harbord, Chairman of New York Chapter American Red Cross, November 11, 1937, dealing with the devastating floods in Mississippi in 1936 and Red Cross response
    - Correspondence "Publicity", January-March 1937 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", April-May 1936 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 9)
      Letters discuss economic conditions of the Philippine Islands and Harbord's address to volunteers of the Red Cross; also includes booklet, "The Constitution of the United States of America, and What it Contains," meant to be an educational pamphlet; Boy Scout ephemera, and Harbord's address to the Boy Scouts; and ephemera from Cody, Wyoming.
    - Correspondence "Publicity", June-December 1936 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 10)
      Notable correspondents include Robert C. Kennedy. Letters discuss Mrs. Harbord's health; trip to Asheville, NC; Requests for speaking engagements, letters, autographed photos, etc. Also includes a copy of "Military Training as a Preparation for Citizenship."
    - Correspondence "Publicity", January-March (Offsite-box 40, Folder 11)
      Includes address, "Military Training as Preparation for Citizenship"
    - Correspondence "Publicity", April-September 1935 (Offsite-box 40, Folder 12)
      Includes General Pershing Birthday Broadcast, September 1935; "Unchanging Facts in Our Changing World," address at combined meeting of the Commonwealth and Commercial Clubs of Cincinnati, Ohio, April 26, 1935.
    - Correspondence "Publicity", October-December 1935 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 1)
      Letters discuss Mrs. Harbord's illness and the New Deal; includes many Invitations to attend/speak at lectures, symposia, society dinners, and other gatherings. Also includes copy of Labor: National Weekly Newspaper Owned and Edited by the Railroad Workers of America.
    - Correspondence "Publicity", July-September 1934 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", January-March 1935 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 2)
      Includes copy of "Again we dream while clouds gather"-- address made at Town Hall January 3, 1935 to NY Chamber of Commerce, Committee On National Defense.
    - Correspondence "Publicity", October-December 1934 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 3)
      Includes copy of Harbord's speech "War in the Air" October 12, 1934 and radio address on "The Chartered Activities of the Red Cross." Also includes letter from Secretary of War General MacArthur.
    - Correspondence "Publicity", May-June 1934 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 5)
      Includes copy of Harbord's "The Story of the Roosevelt Division." Of note is letter from Harbord to E. Edwin Goldwasser, Greater New York Campaign of the United Jewish appeal, dated May 10, 1934: "I have your letter of May 8 requesting a statement endorsing your campaign to raise $1,200,000 for the relief of the Jews of Germany. Inasmuch as I doubt the advisability of initiating such a campaign at a time when there are so many other demands being made on the citizens of this country, I would prefer not to make any statement in this connection."
    - Correspondence "Publicity", January-April 1934 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 6)
      Includes Harbord's address: "Radio in War" and his article "When the Flag Came Down at Corregidor."
    - Correspondence "Publicity", September-December 1933 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 7)
      Includes Harbord's address at Annual Meeting of Philippine Club, December 16th, 1933. Also includes biographical material.
    - Correspondence "Publicity", May-August 1933 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 8)
      Includes copy of "Nylic Review" (Harbord on the cover).
    - Correspondence "Publicity", April 1933 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 9)
      Includes list of "Officers of the Army"
    - Correspondence "Publicity", March 1933 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 10)
      Includes "Annual All Star Show and Fashion Revue of the Israel Orphan Asylum" 1933; address by Harbord before the Pan American Medical Congress at Dallas, TX March 23, 1933: "Closer Relations Between the Republics of the Western Hemisphere".
    - Correspondence "Publicity", January-February 1933 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 11)
      Includes 25th anniversary of the Mental Hygiene Movement, with pamphlet - "A Mind that Found Itself."
    - Correspondence "Publicity", October-December 1932 (Offsite-box 41, Folder 12)
      Includes Harbord's address "Reminiscences of the French High Command;" President Hoover's stand on prohibition; copies of "Recruiting News" containing article on Frazier Hunt's biographical radio talk "Great Personalities"
    - Correspondence "Publicity", July-September 1932 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", April-June 1932 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", May 1932 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", March 1932 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "Publicity", February 1932 (Offsite-box 42, Folder 5)